[
    {
        "front": "じつは",
        "back": "actually",
        "chapter": "N4 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "けいたい(でんわ)",
        "back": "mobile phone",
        "chapter": "N4 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "なくす",
        "back": "to lose (t.)",
        "chapter": "N4 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "（～が）なくなる",
        "back": "dissappear",
        "chapter": "N4 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "はっきり",
        "back": "clearly; in a straightforward manner",
        "chapter": "N4 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "さいご",
        "back": "the last time",
        "chapter": "N4 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "さいしょ",
        "back": "the first (time)",
        "chapter": "N4 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "よる",
        "back": "to stop by",
        "chapter": "N4 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "おとす",
        "back": "to drop (tr.)",
        "chapter": "N4 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "（～が）おちる",
        "back": "to drop (i.)",
        "chapter": "N4 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "けいさつ",
        "back": "police",
        "chapter": "N4 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "けいかん",
        "back": "policeman",
        "chapter": "N4 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひろう",
        "back": "to pick up",
        "chapter": "N4 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "みつかる",
        "back": "to be found",
        "chapter": "N4 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "（～を）みつける",
        "back": "to find",
        "chapter": "N4 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "すり",
        "back": "pick pocket",
        "chapter": "N4 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "どろぼう",
        "back": "thief",
        "chapter": "N4 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぬすむ",
        "back": "to steal",
        "chapter": "N4 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "にげる",
        "back": "to run away",
        "chapter": "N4 C22"
    },
    {
        "front": "つかまえる",
        "back": "to catch",
        "chapter": "N4 C22"
    }
]